Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Information File, Section 3: Boxes 46-66
6047
Kheel Center
109 linear ft.
Records.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into five sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-43
Section 3: Boxes 46-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Boxes 44-45 and 102-109 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Form and Genre Terms:
Records.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6047: Archives Information File
6047: Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
6047: Archives Information File, Section 2: Boxes 23-43
6047: Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
6047: Archives Information File, Section 5: Boxes 89-101
Boxes 44-45 and 102-109 have not been inventoried at this time.
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 46, Folder: 1 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Faits et Chiffres Relatifs a L'Emploi et au Chomage, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: Ch. Bettelheim
    Format: Publication
    Language: French.
  - Item 2: More Facts on Technology & Employment, 1936; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: Machinery and Allied Products Institute
    Notes: April 1936
    Language: English.
  - Item 3: Area Manpower Review, 1969; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: Robert Bidstrup
    Notes: December 1969
  - Item 4: Manpower Requirements for the U.A.R. for the Period 1960-1985, 1964; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: Mostafa Hamdy
    Notes: May 26, 1964
  - Item 5: Report of the 1967/68 Labour Census of Botswana, 1969; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: T.P. Pratt
  - Item 6: Employment in Appalachia Trends and Prospects, 1968; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: Theodore E. Fuller
    Notes: June 1968
  - Item 7: Manpower in Tulsa, 1965; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: Oklahoma Employment Security Commission
    Notes: May 1965
  - Item 8: Schuyler County Manpower Survey, 1969; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: New York Department of Labor
    Notes: July 1969
  - Item 9: East Bay Manpower Survey, 1967; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: California Department of Employment
    Notes: July 1967
  - Item 10: Documents et Travaux, 1966; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: H. Correa, C.M. Loriaux
    Notes: October 1966
  - Item 11: Die Arbeitsamter Unter Dem Faschismus, 1966; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: Franz Danimann
  - Item 12: Labor Force: Vermont, 1963; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: Sargent-Webster-Crenshaw & Folley
    Notes: November 1963
  - Item 13: Newark, New Jersey: Population and Labor Force, 1967; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: Jack Chernick, Bernard P. Indik, George Sternlieb
    Notes: Spring 1967
  - Item 14: Trenton Labor Area Profile, 1966; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Author: New Jersey Division of Employment Security
    Notes: March 1966
  - Item 15: Seneca County Manpower Survey, 1972; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Notes: July 1972
  - Item 16: Delaware County Manpower Survey, 1967; Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
    Notes: December 1967
- Box: 46, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of the African Seminar on Labour Statistics, 1964; Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Author: United Nations
    Notes: December 11, 1964
- Box: 46, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: High-Level Manpower for East Africa's Manufacturing Sector: The Next 10-15 Years, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Author: Peter McLoughlin Associates Ltd.
  - Item 2: An African Labour Force, 1956; Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Author: W. Elkan
- Box: 46, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Sociological Survey of an African Commercial Labour Force, 1953; Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Author: Ellen Hellmann
  - Item 2: Labour in South Africa, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
    Author: South African Economic Research Bureau
- Box: 46, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor in the European Community, 1964; Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
    Author: Adhemar Byl
    Notes: December 1964
- Box: 46, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Dynamics of Small Area Labor Supply: A Case Study, 1967; Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Author: University of Arkansas
    Notes: September 1967
  - Item 2: Arkansas' Industrial Progress, 1950-1968, 1969; Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Author: Arkansas Department of Labor
    Notes: March 1969
  - Item 3: Arkansas's Population and Employment: The Recent Past, the Present, and the Future, 1964; Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Author: Forrest H. Pollard, Ethel B. Jones
    Notes: May 1964
  - Item 4: Local Labor Surveys, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Arkansas Labor Surplus Estimates, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Arkansas' Manpower Needs, 1970; Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Notes: February 1970
- Box: 46, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Arizona's Manpower Challenge of the 60's, 1960; Publication (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Author: James A. Rork
  - Item 2: The Economy of Arizona, 1964; Publication (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Author: Arizona Unemployment Compensation Division
    Notes: February 1964
  - Item 3: Manpower Information Bibliography, 1970; Publication (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Author: Arizona State Employment Service
- Box: 46, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Males and Females in the Work Force Classified According to Industry in Conjunction with Occupational Status, 1961; Publication (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Author: Commonwealth Bureau of Census and Statistics
    Notes: June 30, 1961
  - Item 2: Supplement to the Treasury Information Bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 46, Folder 8)
    Author: Commonwealth Treasury
    Notes: April 1965
- Box: 46, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Baltimore's Occupational Outlook, Publication (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Author: Maryland Department of Employment Security
- Box: 46, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Selected Bibliography on Manpower and Employment, 1965; Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Author: U.S. Department of Labor
    Notes: October 4, 1965
  - Item 2: Manpower Information, 1966; Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Box: 46, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Birmingham Employment Review, 1966; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Author: Alabama Department of Industrial Relations
- Box: 46, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Changing Labor Supply Characteristics Along Route 128, 1961; Publication (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Author: Federal Reserve Bank of Boston
- Box: 46, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: California Labor Force Projections, 1965; Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
    Author: Maurice I. Gershenson
    Notes: May 18, 1965
  - Item 2: Postwar Employment in California, 1945; Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
    Author: California State Reconstruction and Reemployment Commission
    Notes: September 1945
- Box: 46, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Employment Challenge in the 1960's, 1963; Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
    Author: National Industrial Conference Board
    Notes: July 1963
  - Item 2: Changes in Population and in the Labour Force, 1946; Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
    Author: Canada Department of Labour
  - Item 3: Trade Unions and Collective Bargaining in Canada, Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
    Author: Arthur M. Kruger
  - Item 4: Manpower Trends in Canada, Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Projection of the Occupational Composition of the Ontario Labour Force, Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
    Author: Ontario Department of Labour
  - Item 6: Canada's Manpower Requirements, 1968; Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
    Author: Noah M. Meltz & G. Peter Penz
  - Item 7: Industry, Occupation, Earnings, Employment, Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
    Author: Nova Scotia Department of Labour
- Box: 46, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Total Work Force Employment and Unemployment in the Chicago SMSA, Publication (Box 46, Folder 15)
    Author: Illinois Department of Labor
  - Item 2: Total Work Force Employment and Unemployment in the Chicago SMSA, Publication (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Recipients of the Total Work Force, 1967; Publication (Box 46, Folder 15)
    Notes: May 26, 1967
  - Item 4: The Labor Force, City of Chicago and Chicago Metropolitan, 1949; Publication (Box 46, Folder 15)
    Author: University of Chicago
    Notes: December 9, 1949
- Box: 46, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Occupational Composition of the Labor Force, 1960, Publication (Box 46, Folder 16)
    Author: University of Connecticut
  - Item 2: Policy and Program Research in a University Setting, 1971; Publication (Box 46, Folder 16)
    Author: National Academy of Services
  - Item 3: Labour and the Gold Fields, 1968; Publication (Box 46, Folder 16)
    Author: Australian Society for the Study of Labour History
  - Item 4: Labor Trends and Unemployment in Connecticut and the Northeast Region, 1966; Publication (Box 46, Folder 16)
    Author: Edward G. Stockwell, Harold F. Goldsmith
    Notes: December 1966
  - Item 5: The Face of Labour, Publication (Box 46, Folder 16)
    Author: Canadian Broadcasting Corporation
- Box: 46, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Sex, Age, and Level of Skill of the Nonagricultural Labor Force of Mainland China, 1965; Publication (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Author: John Philip Emerson
    Notes: June 1965
- Box: 46, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Area Skills Survey, 1963; Publication (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Author: University of Delaware
- Box: 46, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Employment and Income by Age, Sex, Color and Residence, 1963; Publication (Box 46, Folder 19)
    Author: Detroit Commission on Community Relations
    Notes: May 1963
- Box: 46, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: A Limited Bibliography on Population and Manpower Problems, 1961; Publication (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Author: A.M. Farrag
    Notes: August 3, 1961
- Box: 46, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Die Freizugigkeit der Arbeitskrafte in Europa und der Schweiz, 1966; Publication (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Author: Heinz Allenspach
    Notes: January 1966
    Language: German.
  - Item 2: Manpower Programs as Related to a Policy of Full Employment, 1963; Publication (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Author: Alfred L. Green
    Notes: September 1963
- Box: 46, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Arbeidsmarkeds-Og Distriktspolitikk, Publication (Box 46, Folder 22)
    Author: Bernt Frydenberg
    Language: Norwegian.
- Box: 46, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Labour Reports, 1966; Publication (Box 46, Folder 23)
    Author: Ministry of Communications and Public Works
    Language: Finnish.
- Box: 46, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Situation du Marche de L'Emploi en 1966, Publication (Box 46, Folder 24)
    Author: Office National de L'Emploi
  - Item 2: Beskaeftigelsesprognoser I Frankrig, 1966; Publication (Box 46, Folder 24)
    Author: OECD Projekt
    Notes: May 1966
- Box: 46, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Occupational Trends in Georgia, Publication (Box 46, Folder 25)
    Author: Norman J. Wood
  - Item 2: Annual Average Work Force Estimates by Area, 1968; Publication (Box 46, Folder 25)
    Author: Geogia Department of Labor
  - Item 3: Georgia Employment Trends, 1970; Publication (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Box: 46, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Die Arbeiter und Angestellten nach Beruf und Alter sowie Die Lehrlingshaltung in der Bundesrepublik Deutschland, 1950; Publication (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Author: Bundesministerium fur Arbeit
    Notes: October 31, 1950
  - Item 2: Arbeitsmarkt und Arbeitspartner, Publication (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Author: Herausgegeben vom Presse
  - Item 3: Salzgitter in Zahlen, 1965; Publication (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Author: Herausgegeben vom amt Furwirtschaft U. Statistik der Stadt Salzgitter
- Box: 47, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Greater Accra Employment Market Report for the Quarter, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Author: Ghana Labour Department
  - Item 2: Survey of High-Level Manpower in Ghana, 1961; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Author: Ghana Ministry of Information and Broadcasting
- Box: 47, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Main Results of the Recent Censuses and Manpower Surveys in Greece, 1967; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Author: National Statistical Service of Greece
- Box: 47, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Occupational Employment Trends, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Author: Hawaii Department of Labor and Industrial Relations
    Notes: September 1966
  - Item 2: Oahu Looks Forward to 1961, 1958; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: June 1958
- Box: 47, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employment and Labor Force in Different Industries and Localities in Idaho, 1962; Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Author: Reuben R. Wagner, Norman Nybroten, Russell L. Chrysler
    Notes: October 1962
  - Item 2: Labor Force and Career Plans of High School Seniors in Ten Countries in Southern Idaho, Publication (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Author: Norman Nybroten
- Box: 47, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Illinois Total Civilian Work Force, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Labor Force Projections for 1970, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Decatur Blueprint for Manpower, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Du Page County Manpower Profile, Publication (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Author: Illinois State Employment Service
- Box: 47, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Survey of Ex-Technical Trainees Registered with Employment Exchanges in Madhya Pradesh, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Author: National Employment Service
    Notes: June 30, 1965
  - Item 2: Standards for Surveys on Labour Force, Employment and Unemployment, 1961; Publication (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Author: India Department of Statistics
    Notes: June 1961
- Box: 47, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Indiana Manpower Trends to 1975, Publication (Box 47, Folder 7)
    Author: Indiana Employment Security Division
  - Item 2: Job Mobility and Migration, 1960; Publication (Box 47, Folder 7)
    Author: Purdue University
    Notes: November 1960
  - Item 3: Indiana Labor Force Employment and Unemployment, Publication (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Area Trends in Employment and Unemployment, Publication (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Indiana Manpower Projections, Publication (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Box: 47, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: This is Humboldt County, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
    Author: Iowa Employment Security Commission
    Notes: September 1965
  - Item 2: Occupational Projections for Iowa, 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 8)
    Author: Catherine A. Palomba
- Box: 47, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Regional Employment Patterns in the Republic of Ireland, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 9)
    Author: T.J. Baker
    Notes: August 1966
- Box: 47, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Opinions of the Japanese Top Company Executives on the Social Conditions Closely Relating to the Long-Rage Development of Business and Industry, 1963; Publication (Box 47, Folder 10)
    Author: Yasuo Kotaka
    Notes: March 1963
- Box: 47, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Skills for the Future, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 11)
    Author: Kalamazoo County Manpower Committee
- Box: 47, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Manpower Developments in Wichita, KS, 1963; Publication (Box 47, Folder 12)
    Author: University of Wichita
    Notes: January 1963
  - Item 2: Statewide Employment Statistics, Publication (Box 47, Folder 12)
    Author: Kansas Department of Labor
  - Item 3: Manpower in Kansas, Publication (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Box: 47, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Resources of Adair County, KY, Publication (Box 47, Folder 13)
    Author: Kentucky Division of Employment Service
- Box: 47, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Kentucky Occupational Trends from 1950 to 1960 with Projections to 1975, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 14)
    Author: Fulmer
  - Item 2: Kentucky Employment Trends from 1951 to 1963 with Projections to 1965-75, Publication (Box 47, Folder 14)
    Author: Fulmer & Pitts
- Box: 47, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: High-Level Manpower Requirements and Resources in Kenya, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 15)
    Author: Kenya Ministry of Economic Planning and Development
- Box: 47, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Manpower Outlook to 1985, 1968; Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
    Author: Louisiana Department of Employment Security
    Notes: September 1968
  - Item 2: Migration of Working Aged Population, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
    Author: Louisiana State University
  - Item 3: The Labor Market in the Lower Mississippi River Industrial Area, 1957; Publication (Box 47, Folder 16)
    Author: Louisiana Division of Employment Security
    Notes: August 1957
- Box: 47, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Occupational Outlook: Cumberland Job Market Area, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 17)
    Notes: November 1966
- Box: 47, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Massachusetts Cities and Towns, Publication (Box 47, Folder 18)
    Author: Massachusetts Division of Employment Security
- Box: 47, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Manpower in Michigan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 19)
    Author: Michigan Employment Security Commission
  - Item 2: Manpower in Michigan, Publication (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: Projections of Labor Demand and Supply, Publication (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Item 4: Reaching for Equality, Publication (Box 47, Folder 19)
    Author: Michigan Civil Rights Commission
  - Item 5: The Michigan Manpower Study, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 19)
    Author: Battelle Memorial Institute
    Notes: May 18, 1966
- Box: 47, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Occupational Outlook, Publication (Box 47, Folder 20)
    Author: Minnesota Department of Employment Security
- Box: 47, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: A Skill Survey: Minnesota's Minneapolis- St. Paul Area, Publication (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Box: 47, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Tijdelijke Werkkrachten, Publication (Box 47, Folder 22)
    Author: Manpower
    Language: Dutch.
  - Item 2: Arbeidsmarkt en Loonpolitiek, Publication (Box 47, Folder 22)
    Author: N.E.H. van Esveld
- Box: 47, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Nevada Work Force Historical Series, 1969; Publication (Box 47, Folder 23)
    Author: Nevada Employment Security Department
    Notes: October 1969
- Box: 47, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: New England Labor and the Economy at the Year-End, Publication (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Box: 47, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Population and Employment Changes in the 42 Job Centers of New Hampshire, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    Author: New Hampshire Department of Employment Security
  - Item 2: Growth and Decline in New Hampshire Industries, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Population and Employment Changes in the 38 Job Centers of New Hampshire, 1967; Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
    Notes: October 1967
  - Item 4: Population and Employment Changes in the 42 Job Centers of New Hampshire, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Available Workers Living in New Hampshire and Characteristics of the Labor Supply, Publication (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Box: 47, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: A Digest of Employment, Publication (Box 47, Folder 26)
    Author: New Jersey Department of Conservation and Economic Development
  - Item 2: Camden Labor Area Profile, 1968; Publication (Box 47, Folder 26)
    Notes: March 1968
  - Item 3: Atlantic City Labor Market Area Profile, 1963; Publication (Box 47, Folder 26)
    Notes: June 1963
- Box: 47, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Employment Opportunities and Training Needs for Technicians in the State of Missouri, Publication (Box 47, Folder 27)
    Author: University of Missouri
  - Item 2: Employment Opportunities and Training Needs for Skilled Workers in the State of Missouri, Publication (Box 47, Folder 27)
    Author: James C. Warner
  - Item 3: Employment Opportunities and Training Needs for Selected Service Workers in the State of Missouri, Publication (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Box: 47, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Manpower Outlook, Publication (Box 47, Folder 28)
    Author: New York City Department of Labor
  - Item 2: Manpower Problems in New York City, 1968; Publication (Box 47, Folder 28)
    Author: Abraham C. Burstein
    Notes: April 22, 1968
  - Item 3: The Job Situation in New York, 1967; Publication (Box 47, Folder 28)
    Notes: December 18, 1967
  - Item 4: Interim Market Area Report, 1969; Publication (Box 47, Folder 28)
    Notes: February 1969
- Box: 47, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Binghamton Area, 1971; Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Westchester-Rockland Area, 1971; Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Syracuse Labor Area, 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Albany-Schenectady-Troy, 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Nassau-Suffolk Area, 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: New York City Area, 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Item 7: Utica-Rowe Labor Area, 1969; Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Item 8: Buffalo Labor Area, 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Item 9: Manpower and Technological Change in New York State, Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Item 10: A Look Ahead at Long Island Employment, Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
    Author: William Hamovitch, Albert M. Levenson, Alfred J. Van Tassel
  - Item 11: The Manpower Crisis, 1967; Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
    Author: Special Senate Committee on Manpower
  - Item 12: Manpower Outlook and Training Needs, Publication (Box 47, Folder 29)
- Box: 47, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Age, Sex, and Occupation of Applicants for Work in New York City, 1939; Publication (Box 47, Folder 30)
    Notes: December 1939
  - Item 2: Occupations of Applicants for Work, 1939; Publication (Box 47, Folder 30)
    Notes: September 1939
  - Item 3: Labor Market Outlook, 1947; Publication (Box 47, Folder 30)
    Notes: November 1947
- Box: 47, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The Next Twenty Years, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 31)
    Author: Port of New York Authority